[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "So can we take the mere fact that you are on board as a sign that he's getting serious?", "question_tokens": ["So", "can", "we", "take", "the", "mere", "fact", "that", "you", "are", "on", "board", "as", "a", "sign", "that", "he", "'s", "getting", "serious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Well, this campaign is much more consequential than any couple of hires, but the reason he's risen in the polls is very simple.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "campaign", "is", "much", "more", "consequential", "than", "any", "couple", "of", "hires", ",", "but", "the", "reason", "he", "'s", "risen", "in", "the", "polls", "is", "very", "simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Are we really going to have the debate about who's the more -- reliable conservative if you're representing Governor Romney, Senator Talent?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "really", "going", "to", "have", "the", "debate", "about", "who", "'s", "the", "more", "--", "reliable", "conservative", "if", "you", "'re", "representing", "Governor", "Romney", ",", "Senator", "Talent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", ":", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "You know --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Piers, can I answer that?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "can", "I", "answer", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Whoa, whoa.", "answer_tokens": ["Whoa", ",", "whoa", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "You respond to what Kellyanne said, by all means, but also what are you going to do about the fact that all the momentum is now with your rival?", "question_tokens": ["You", "respond", "to", "what", "Kellyanne", "said", ",", "by", "all", "means", ",", "but", "also", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "all", "the", "momentum", "is", "now", "with", "your", "rival", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, look, this is a debate that we need to have.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "this", "is", "a", "debate", "that", "we", "need", "to", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kellyanne"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Is Newt Gingrich really geared up, do you think, as the opponent, for the long haul?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Newt", "Gingrich", "really", "geared", "up", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "as", "the", "opponent", ",", "for", "the", "long", "haul", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, we are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Do you think he can do that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "can", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "He can and he has.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "can", "and", "he", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "From your perspective, obviously, you have to remain fairly neutral at the moment, but how are you viewing the race as it's progressing?", "question_tokens": ["From", "your", "perspective", ",", "obviously", ",", "you", "have", "to", "remain", "fairly", "neutral", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "but", "how", "are", "you", "viewing", "the", "race", "as", "it", "'s", "progressing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, I don't know if the gloves are off.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "the", "gloves", "are", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I'm very well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "I mean can you see any of the other candidates really making much of a push at this stage?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "can", "you", "see", "any", "of", "the", "other", "candidates", "really", "making", "much", "of", "a", "push", "at", "this", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I watched the debates, you know, on Saturday night.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "watched", "the", "debates", ",", "you", "know", ",", "on", "Saturday", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "I mean what is your expert assessment of the two candidates?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "is", "your", "expert", "assessment", "of", "the", "two", "candidates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I think -- I think that's a pretty good assessment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "pretty", "good", "assessment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "And he just exacerbated that, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "just", "exacerbated", "that", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Well, that's one of the things that you fear going into a debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "you", "fear", "going", "into", "a", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What are you seeing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "seeing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "I think that's absolutely right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "absolutely", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Who would be, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Well, I think --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What do you make of this surge by former Speaker Gingrich?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "surge", "by", "former", "Speaker", "Gingrich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "He's somebody who has been around a long time and is good on TV, is good in debates and -- you know, but Mitt Romney has shown himself to be somebody who is good at politics as well.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "somebody", "who", "has", "been", "around", "a", "long", "time", "and", "is", "good", "on", "TV", ",", "is", "good", "in", "debates", "and", "--", "you", "know", ",", "but", "Mitt", "Romney", "has", "shown", "himself", "to", "be", "somebody", "who", "is", "good", "at", "politics", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Should we read into that that they're probably more worried about Newt Gingrich?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "we", "read", "into", "that", "that", "they", "'re", "probably", "more", "worried", "about", "Newt", "Gingrich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I would give them some advice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "give", "them", "some", "advice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "It was all a bit of a storm in a teacup, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "all", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "storm", "in", "a", "teacup", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "It sure was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "sure", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Do they?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I don't believe they do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "believe", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Bloomberg"]}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "But what are your views generally about who the next mayor perhaps ought to be?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "are", "your", "views", "generally", "about", "who", "the", "next", "mayor", "perhaps", "ought", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "MD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, I think it's going to be really hard to follow Mike Bloomberg.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "really", "hard", "to", "follow", "Mike", "Bloomberg", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Where do you think he is right now, given all that's been going on?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "he", "is", "right", "now", ",", "given", "all", "that", "'s", "been", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "When I see a speech like that, it looks like he's getting ready to fight and take some numbers.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "see", "a", "speech", "like", "that", ",", "it", "looks", "like", "he", "'s", "getting", "ready", "to", "fight", "and", "take", "some", "numbers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "What do you think of the way their race is going?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "way", "their", "race", "is", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I don't think it's going very well at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "very", "well", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "It seems a bit trite to say that, because in any kind of society where you have this kind of financial meltdown, isn't it instinctively the right thing not do, that the rich should contribute a little bit more to the recovery than those with no money?", "question_tokens": ["It", "seems", "a", "bit", "trite", "to", "say", "that", ",", "because", "in", "any", "kind", "of", "society", "where", "you", "have", "this", "kind", "of", "financial", "meltdown", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "instinctively", "the", "right", "thing", "not", "do", ",", "that", "the", "rich", "should", "contribute", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "to", "the", "recovery", "than", "those", "with", "no", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I think people like Warren Buffett -- I'm not in his class.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "like", "Warren", "Buffett", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "in", "his", "class", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Who do you think is going to be the Republican nominee, as we sit here today?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "is", "going", "to", "be", "the", "Republican", "nominee", ",", "as", "we", "sit", "here", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "I'm a movie maker.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "movie", "maker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["King Solomon"]}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "So what do you want to win?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "do", "you", "want", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Here's how it happens -- this is -- this is where King Solomon taught me a great lesson.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "how", "it", "happens", "--", "this", "is", "--", "this", "is", "where", "King", "Solomon", "taught", "me", "a", "great", "lesson", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Thatcher"]}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Wouldn't that be a nice night if they both won?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "that", "be", "a", "nice", "night", "if", "they", "both", "won", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Tell me about Margaret Thatcher.", "answer_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "Margaret", "Thatcher", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111212pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "What did you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Listen, that's a sexy, fun, entertaining movie.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "sexy", ",", "fun", ",", "entertaining", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]